Finding aid to the Alumnae Groups records CA.MS.01014
Smith College Archives
Alumnae Groups records
1887-2009
Smith College Archives
Smith College -- Alumni and alumnae.
CA.MS.01014
19.875 linear feet (57 containers)
The collection contains records of the Alumnae Association and Smith Clubs.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials in the Smith College Archives are open for use, with the following exceptions: "Office Files," files of records created for the use of the administrative unit that created them, are closed to research for a period of 10 years following their creation. In all cases, the College Archives will continue to provide public access to materials that were intended to be public at the time of their creation (press releases, publications, etc.)
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Source unknown.
Other Finding Aids
Many parts of the collection have container lists that are available upon request by contacting specialcollections@smith.edu
Related Materials
Alumnae Association records
Scope and Contents
The collection contains records of the Alumnae Association and Smith Clubs.
Smith College--Alumni and alumnae; Smith College. Alumni Association; Smith College.
- General, A-C (Box 3122)
- Candidates' Committee (Box 3122.1)
- Smith Clubs, General (Box 3123)
- Smith Clubs, A-Ce (Box 3124)
- Smith Clubs, Cen (Box 3124.1)
- Smith Clubs, Ce-Ci (Box 3124.2)
- Smith Clubs, Chicago (includes North Shore) (Box 3124.2a)
- Smith Clubs, Cl-K (Box 3124.3)
- Smith Clubs, L - New York (Box 3124.4)
- Smith Clubs, Newt - R (Box 3125)
- Smith Clubs, S-Z (Box 3126)
- Smith Clubs, Westchester, NY (Box 3126.1)
- Smith Clubs, Belmont/Arlington/Lexington/Waltham, MA (Box 3126.2)
- Smith Clubs, Boston (Box 3127)
- Smith Clubs, Boston, Minutes, 1887-1951 (Box 3128)
- Smith Clubs, Boston, Minutes, 1951-1971 (Box 3129)
- Smith Clubs, Boston, Programs and Directory, 1892-1978 (Box 3130)
- Smith Clubs, Boston, Treasurer's Reports, 1887-1955 (Box 3131)
- Smith Clubs, Boston, Checkbooks (Box 3131)
- Smith Clubs, Boston, Records, 1992-2008 (Box 3131.1)
- Smith Clubs, Boston League of Smith College Clubs (Box 3132)
- Smith Clubs, Dallas, Book Sales (Box 3133.1)
- Smith Clubs, Dallas (Box 3133.1a)
- Smith Clubs, Franklin County (Box 3133.2)
- Smith Clubs, Hampshire County, Records, 1920-1956 (Box 3134)
- Smith Clubs, Hampshire County, Directory, Newsletter, Records, 1956-2003 (Box 3134.1)
- Smith Clubs, Hampshire County, Records, 1992-2009 (Box 3135)
- Smith Clubs, Minnesota (Box 3135.1)
- Smith Clubs, Orange City, CA (Box 3136.1)
- Smith Clubs, Pittsburgh, A-L (Box 3137)
- Smith Clubs, Pittsburgh, M-Z (Box 3138)
- Smith Clubs, Rhode Island, 1913-2001 (Box 3138.1)
- Smith Clubs, Rhode Island, general scrapbook (Box 3138.1)
- Smith Clubs, St Louis (Box 3139)
- Smith Clubs, Taconic Area (Box 3140)
- Smith Clubs, Worcester (Box 3140.1)
- Smith Clubs, Worcester, Centennial Exhibit, 1993-1994 (Box 3140.1)
- Smith Clubs, Lists of officers, newsletters, 1984-2006 (Box 3140.2)
- Alumnae Association Council, 1915-1935 (Box 3141)
- Alumnae Association Council, 1936-1954 (Box 3142)
- Alumnae Association Council, 1955-1990; n.d. (Box 3143)
- General, D-F (Box 3144)
- Directed reading lists (Box 3145)
- General, G-L (Box 3144.1)
- Lesbianism (Box 3144.2)
- General, M-O (Box 3146)
- Non-graduate Association (Box 3147)
- General, P-T (Box 3148)
- General, V-Z (Box 3148.1)
- Reorganization and Membership Drive (Box 3149)
- Reunions, general (Box 3150)
- Reunions, A-Parades, 1912-1979 (Box 3150)
- Reunions, Parades, 1980-1989 (Box 3150.1)
- Reunions, Remembrance Service (Box 3150.1)
- Reunions, List of Attendees, 1987-1995 (Box 3150.2)
- Reunions, List of Attendees, 1996-2009 (Box 3150.3)
- Alumnae Weekend (Box 3151)
- Publications, Alumni Opinion on the Future of Smith College, 1946 (Box 3152)
- Publications, Annual reports (Box 3152)
- Publications (Box 3153)
- Publications (Box 3153.1)
- Smith Alumnae Quarterly, Board meetings (Box 3153.1a)
- Smith Alumnae Quarterly, miscellaneous A-Z (Box 3154)